[
  {
    "front": "incomprehensibility",
    "back": "n. 难解；不可思议",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ɪnˌkɒmprɪˌhensəˈbɪləti/"
  },
  {
    "front": "characterization",
    "back": "n. 描述；特性描述",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌkærəktəraɪˈzeɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "intercommunication",
    "back": "n. 互相通信；互通消息",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌɪntəkəˌmjuːnɪˈkeɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "misunderstanding",
    "back": "n. 误解；误会",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌmɪsʌndəˈstændɪŋ/"
  },
  {
    "front": "underestimation",
    "back": "n. 低估；轻视",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌʌndərˌestɪˈmeɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "acknowledgement",
    "back": "n. 承认；确认；感谢",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/əkˈnɒlɪdʒmənt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "disappointment",
    "back": "n. 失望；沮丧",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌdɪsəˈpɔɪntmənt/"
  },
  {
    "front": "responsibility",
    "back": "n. 责任；职责",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/rɪˌspɒnsəˈbɪləti/"
  },
  {
    "front": "administration",
    "back": "n. 管理；行政；实施",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ədˌmɪnɪˈstreɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "representative",
    "back": "n. 代表；典型",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌreprɪˈzentətɪv/"
  },
  {
    "front": "recommendation",
    "back": "n. 推荐；建议",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌrekəmenˈdeɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "transportation",
    "back": "n. 运输；运输系统",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌtrænspɔːˈteɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "transformation",
    "back": "n. 转化；转换；改革",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌtrænsfəˈmeɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "identification",
    "back": "n. 鉴定；识别；认同",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/aɪˌdentɪfɪˈkeɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "investigation",
    "back": "n. 调查；研究",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ɪnˌvestɪˈgeɪʃn/"
  },
  {
    "front": "psychological",
    "back": "adj. 心理的；心理学的",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌsaɪkəˈlɒdʒɪkl/"
  },
  {
    "front": "extraordinary",
    "back": "adj. 非凡的；特别的",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ɪkˈstrɔːdnri/"
  },
  {
    "front": "international",
    "back": "adj. 国际的",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ˌɪntəˈnæʃnəl/"
  },
  {
    "front": "environmental",
    "back": "adj. 环境的；周围的",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/ɪnˌvaɪrənˈmentl/"
  },
  {
    "front": "communication",
    "back": "n. 通讯；交流",
    "note": "Long Words",
    "phonetic": "/kəˌmjuːnɪˈkeɪʃn/"
  }
]